

# HTUN HTUN OO

Power Platform Specialist

+959 255961269

xtunoo@gmail.com

<u>htunoo.github.io</u>

• 635, 10th Ward, Hlaing Twsp, Yangon

# **EDUCATION**

B.C.Sc Computer University, Thaton 2013 - 2018

## **SKILLS**

- UI/UX
- HTML, CSS, PHP
- Javascript, Typescript,
- Ionic, Android & iOS
- Adobe Photoshop
- MS Power Platform, SharePoint
- MySQL, MS SQL
- · GitHub, Gitlab

# **LANGUAGES**

- ENGLISH
- MYANMAR

## **ABOUT ME**

IT with 4+ years of experience in developing applications with programming languages, frameworks, low-code platforms (Microsoft Power platform), and backend systems I'm still working at City Properties as an IT Officer for developing internal apps with the Microsoft Power Platform. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**IT Officer** 

Apr 2022 - Present

### City Properties Co., Ltd

According to business requirements, we have implemented internal systems such as Utilities Reading & Calculation Report, Budget & Non-budget Request, Diesel Supply & Generator Running Hours, Workforce Requisition, Monthly Invoice for Ferry Management, Fixed Asset Transfer, Meeting Room Request, Car Way Request, Overtime Request by using PowerApps, Power Automate, SharePoint and MS SQL Server. And according to user requirements, we have created PowerBI dashboards for Diesel Price Info, Strategy Dashboard, Lease Rate Dashboard and Footfall Data Dashboard. And we also support the City Properties Single Tenant Migration Process.

IT Officer

Mar 2020 - Apr 2021

#### Kubota Myanmar Co., Ltd

- Monitoring Network and Server Maintenance
- Fix printer, router, PC and system software and other issues
- Prepare projector and other equipment for meeting
- Implement internal portal site using Google Slide (G Suite)

Mobile Developer

Sep 2018 - Feb 2020

### Myanmar Information Technology Pte. Ltd

List of applications implemented for this company:

HCM Connect

To HR processes easier and smoother from the employees' side as well as the HR side, such as attendance (time in/out), QR scan and other features like self-service

Connect Edx

Connect Eax
To make class attendance easier with check in and to report daily, monthly attendance summary easier

Vantage MIT

To give company related information and activities to customer and user